

### KIERRA PALMER

### COMPUTER SCIENCE STUDENT

(208)317-9910 • kierrapalmer@aol.com • icarus.cs.weber.edu/~kp63421/index.html • Ogden,UT

#### PROFILE

My name is Kierra and I am currently a Junior at Weber State University. My major is Computer Science with a minor in Business/Multimedia Technologies. My goal in the next two years is to finish my studies at WSU and hopefully get an internship or job to help expand my knowledge in the technologies world.

#### EDUCATION

2015 - Weber State University current Junior - GPA 3.91

2012 - Boise High School
2015 Class of 2015 - GPA 4.18

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Weber State University • Student Aid Aug 2016-current

Assist in computer science office with any secretarial tasks needed, including but not limited to: copying, filing, creating word and excel documents, and creating event flyers

# Weber State University ● Testing Proctor Aug 2016-current

Check in students and ensure that they have the necessary tools for their test. Proctor students throughout their tests.

Monitor open computer lab and assist with any printing or computer questions.

### Taffy Treasures • Cashier & Graphic Designer Feb 2015 - Mar 2016

Greet customers and assist them with their purchases.

Manage all social media accounts and create documents and promotional posters for all store sales and events

#### SKILLS

Internet Research	
Word	
Excel	
Powerpoint	
TrakAxPC	
Photoshop	
InDesign	
C++	
Java	
HTML	
CSS	
JavaScript/JQuery	
SQL	
x86 Assembler	